(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T08:35:48.878856",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper "Truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring;
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead:
A wild chase, a frantic pace,
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
(Ah… la da da da da da
I'm always spinning fate
Whoah yeah)
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all—
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on,
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string,
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet,
I spin back 'round with every chance I get,
The wheel turns and the die is cast,
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead!
A perfect chance, a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
(Ooh la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoah, yeah)
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead)
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage
to run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea
endlessly, cheerfully, meeting heart to heart!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah!
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far, but we're striving, thriving
Here we are, achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through! (This is it!)
Been smashing barriers left and right (That's our myth!)
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights (It's endless!)
So get together, let's reunite!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways,
Discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step,
gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
with each generation, a shining sensation,
a dream unfurls—
Let's make friends, making a moment of history!
Joyfully, follow me; we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now, setting hearts in motion—
Connecting all of the world!
We're making our way to the next dimension,
We're living out the dreams we believe in,
Excitement beyond our comprehension,
There's no question, we'll break through!
We'll keep aspiring to excel
It's awe-inspiring, going well
So light the fire and let's rebel!
The future's brighter, we can tell!
Yay! Yeah!
Medley, medley, medley, medley!
What are you doing?
Oh, you too! Both of you guys are actually a little strange right now.
We're doing crazy faces!
Why are they being so silly? Come on, we got a show to do!
Ina, come on! Come on! Gambare!
I know the floor is nice, but...
It is really nice. It's smooth.
Minas, thank you for coming to the show today to celebrate Myth's...
You guessed it! 5th Anniversary!
The melody, a nice throwback. We've played so many songs together. Nostalgic!
Putting it all together like that is like, really emotional and moving.
It's not just like our 5th year anniversary, it's also Hololive English as a whole! 5 years!
Yeah! Don't do that!
We're all chibi!
You know, we also teased so much in the last 5 years, you know?
Uh, we had three EN concerts, like World's End, Let's Go...
And we had a lot of friends join us over the years, and you know...
In the end, I'm just really happy to be performing with you guys. It's so much fun.
We can't get too emotional just yet though, because we have a show to do!
It's just... Yes. Anyways, anyways...
There's a hashtag right here, right here. Yes, yes.
Over here, taking lots of pictures, screenshots and post them on social media, #Myth5Years!
Make us trend! Trending, get it trending!
Number one, if you want, you don't have to if you don't want. Just kidding!
If you don't do it, we'll be sad. We'll be angry. We'll get you.
Okay, besides that everybody, this is important.
I'm just checking, making sure you guys are all here legally.
Did you guys all receive a ticket so much?
Did you guys all receive a ticket?
Oh, I remember that. It's me, it's me, that's me!
We look so cool!
Yeah, I think I gave you mine at the bar. It was kind of spicy, remember?
I accosted you on the street, yeah, if you remember that.
Oh, oh, that's what you're up to. I might have pressed...
What? What did you do?
You know, don't do such a thing! What did you do?
You know, don't do such a thing! What did you do? That's our echo.
You know, my Inomai, Inoness...
Sorry. What did you do?
You want to share? Nothing, I did nothing.
Don't tell me your secrets! What you twist been 5 years.
Now that we know that everybody is here with their tickets and they're allowed to be here, we'll be singing a lot on this stage today...
...in different combinations and different fun songs and so on. But speaking of the stage, oh yeah, let's open the stage!
That smooth floor! Beautiful stage! Gorgeous stage!
You really like that one.
Are you feeling that?
Is that a heart?
What's that heart for?
It's sponsored.
Did it just change color? I think it just gained some color.
Oh, why, you wonder? Could it be that it's reacting to
everybody's reactions in the chat and their feelings?
It's changing color according to that. Are you guys getting excited?
Yeah, you guys have an important job to do now, right?
Yeah, but they're always doing something. You guys are always doing things.
It must be their power and their energy. It's flowing through us.
Thank you.
Well, I'm looking forward to seeing how it develops from here out. So you know what you're going to do, right?
You're going to get out your keyboards and you're going to type some things.
Hackerman. Hackerman, yeah.
Give us your energy! Give it to us!
Yeah. No, okay, we're not trying to shake you down or anything. I feel like I'll take them down right now.
Okay, all right, we're choosing violence again today.
Why are you so violent? It's in a violent mood.
Is there a wholesome side? Five years later she's done.
Oh, no, they know the real me. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I feel like I'm always the one that makes it awkward. I apologize.
Yeah, there's not a lot of time for yapping too much today, it would seem. We're gonna dance our hearts out and sing our hearts out for you guys. And
Oh, man, we've been doing a lot of that these days. I think Hololive and Myth deserves a trophy,
a little reward, a reward, a treat, perhaps?
Cookies? Cookies sound good too. Cookies sound good too.
Maybe a cookie-shaped trophy or a trophy-shaped cookie.
Yes. Yes, yeah.
You hear that, management? You better be having some rewards for us. That's not a bad thing. That's okay. In that case, I know how we can kick this off.
Kick it off?
Yeah. So maybe it's like a little cheesy. But I thought maybe the three of us could like jump in the air and go, "Woo!"
like 3, 2, 1, jump! And then the camera goes whew and we're like flying into the air and go to the next song.
I get it, I get it. I get too.
Okay. Done it before. Okay.
Then let's do it. No punching, no violent thoughts, Ena. Don't punch the camera!
I know what you're thinking. Just one uppercut. Not one, not zero.
Okay. Let's do it, okay? Here we go. Am I counting?
Ready? Okay. Next song start! 3, 2, 1, show!
つまらないデイズもう散々ね！
Boring days are already over!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
A life where you're just wishing for miracles
watch me do-do-do-do-do
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Magic without any tricks or secrets
I wanna be free! だってまだフリーさ
I wanna be free! Because I'm still free
(The party ain't started)
Hey タクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey taxi, take me to space for a bit
秒針は音を立てて夜を急かす魔物のように
The second hand, like a monster, ticks loudly, urging the night
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Life is a magic that melts away in an instant
それならば駆け抜けて想い通り！
If that's the case, then run through it as you wish!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってdrivin'
Jump on the playful carriage and start drivin'
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我儘のままに爛れに注意
Be careful not to get caught up in selfishness
洒落た街でdancin'
Dancing in a stylish city
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
Goodbye inferiority complex
何時しかは喝采クラップオウデエンス
Someday, applause from the audience
皆々御詠和あれ！
Everyone, join in!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
混乱がっせても仕樣がない ガラス シューズで踊る tonight
Even if it's chaotic, dancing in glass shoes tonight
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
コンヤニアルサドナイ
There's no tomorrow tonight
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょ？
So, those who dance freely win, right?
d-d-d-d-dance! ラララリホ
d-d-d-d-dance! La la la li ho
どんな問題も解いは一つ
Every problem has only one solution
白紙も 正解も 間違いも 愛す
Love blank papers, correct answers, and mistakes
本当のあたし の 理想
My true ideal
ah なんだか世界は限界の気がして
Ah, the world seems to have limits I can feel
oh ただただ安心じゃ心配
Oh, just being safe is worrying
今 すぐ jumpin', jumpin' out
Jumpin' out right now
chitty chitty bang bang
chitty bang bang
唯々唯々ね危機感抱く日々々に
In days when I feel an urgent crisis
ぎりぎり爆発気味
Explosive feelings are at their limit
たった今発散してしまおうか
Should I let it all out now?
まだまだビイビー弾巧みに乱射
Still firing away skillfully
一発じゃあ撃ち足りないわ
One shot is not enough
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
Finally, I found the answer
灰に成る迄踊って居ろう
Dance until it turns to ash
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
bibbidi bobbidi boowa, yeah
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってdrivin'
Jump on the playful carriage and start drivin'
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我儘のままに爛れに注意
Be careful not to get caught up in selfishness
洒落た街でdancin'
Dancing in a stylish city
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
Goodbye inferiority complex
何時しかは喝采クラップオウデエンス
Someday, applause from the audience
皆々御詠和あれ！
Everyone, join in!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
bibbidi bobbidi boowa, yeah
混乱がっせても仕樣がない
Even if it's chaotic, there's no other way
ガラス シューズで踊る tonight
Dancing in glass shoes tonight
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
bibbidi bobbidi boowa, yeah
コンヤニアルサドナイ
There's no tomorrow tonight
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょ？
So, those who dance freely win, right?
d-d-d-d-dance! ラララリホ
d-d-d-d-dance! La la la li ho
どんな問題も解いは一つ
Every problem has only one solution
白紙も 正解も 間違いも 愛す
Love blank papers, correct answers, and mistakes
本当のあたし の 理想
My true ideal
ah なんだか世界は限界の気がして
Ah, the world seems to have limits I can feel
oh ただただ安心じゃ心配
Oh, just being safe is worrying
今 すぐ jumpin', jumpin' out
Jumpin' out right now
chitty chitty bang bang
chitty bang bang
hurry, let's get it started
濁捏で結構 easy peasy pow
Indulge in the mess, easy peasy pow
頭の中でこねくり回す
Kneading thoughts in my head
後のペルソナに繋がる生まれたてのアイデア
Connecting to the next persona, a newborn idea
多少ムラがあるが疑うこともなく才ある者が群がる
A bit inconsistent, but talented folks gather without doubt
what about you? ただ探求妄想膨らます
What about you? Just expanding my inquiries and fantasies
居場所無い分かれ道の先に待つ結末は
What outcome awaits at the crossroads where I don't belong?
騶虞 麒麟児 大器晩成 はたまた臥竜鳳雛の末端
A prodigy, late bloomer, or just a fledgling hidden dragon
選ぶのは自分 血気盛んに決起
I choose for myself, rising up with fierce spirit
名前と共に残す生きた証 例えばここで言い切った歌詞
Leaving proof of life with my name, like the lyrics declared here
興味本位が充足 光陰矢の如しあっという間
Curiosity fulfilled, time flies like an arrow in a flash
living with no hesitation
時間を忘れて耽る on, and on, and no joke
Losing track of time, absorbed on and on and no joke
kicking back, coming up next level
the future's only colored by the cleverest of rebels
飽和した時代を過去にすべく
To leave the saturated era behind in the past
狂気孕んだ種が芽生出す いずれ実り昇華
Mad seeds sprout, eventually bearing fruit and transcending
乱れ咲いた桜花 浴びるホープ turn it up
Cherry blossoms bloom in disorder, basking in the hope, turn it up
熱狂 just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me
Just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me
熱狂 can't hide, it's a new generation creation
Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
熱狂 tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
熱狂 can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
too wild, too loud
unbound and unrefined
find out that cloud of noise,
it's only in our minds
right now, it's time
no doubt we're moving on
i'm drawing my ideal world outside their lines
思い立ったその瞬間から 気付けば今やもう習慣
From the moment it struck me, before I knew it, it's a habit
wrecking all expectations
初心を忘れず耽る on, and on, and no joke
Never forgetting where I started, on and on and no joke
腐敗する暇なし 鮮やかな眼差し
No time to rot, vibrant gaze
猛った衝動情熱は依然止まらない
Raging urge and passion still won't stop
never hitting the brakes, to prove i got what it takes
and manifest a world you'll never discern as real or fake, so, come on
熱狂 just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me
Just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me
熱狂 can't hide, it's a new generation creation
Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
熱狂 tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
熱狂 can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
人様に誇れずとも 自分の背中押せるような夢があればそれでいい
Even if I can't brag, a dream that pushes my own back is enough
たれるまでで終わるよりも只管にもがく
Rather than fading away, I'll struggle all the more
止まない雨はないと信じ今に様変わる
Believing no rain lasts forever, things will transform
words like gifted, prolific, you better be specific
broad strokes, blowing smoke, blink and you could miss it
these words illicit visions of a future so exquisite
a masterpiece you never seen, awaiting the few committed
知らないことがあれば研究 出来ないことがあれば練習
If I don't know it, research; if I can't do it, practice
姿勢は前傾故の熱中 成功の真反対にある失敗が一番の近道
Leaning forward with passion, failure is the shortest path to success
you can do it さあ行こう時は満ちた it's about time
You can do it, let's go, the time has come, it's about time
stars aligning, i'll design it all i'm already on my way
捩る音が歪み 萌ゆる体内満ちるまで
Distorting sounds, until my blazing body is filled
and if it's lost, i'll find it, all this blind resolve, gotta go it my own way
vicious, and vivid, and striking, my 熱狂
Vicious, and vivid, and striking, my nekkyou
熱狂
Nekkyou
vicious, and vivid, and striking, my 熱狂
Vicious, and vivid, and striking, my nekkyou
熱狂
Nekkyou
誤解すんなよ こんな滑稽な
Don't misunderstand, this ridiculous thing
サッと過ぎ去る 毎日 (エブリデイ)
The everyday life that quickly passes
another prisoner of fate no one could fake out
stay awake now, you know you wanna fire away
now there's no question where the fault lies
these days i struggle just to empathize
もう戻らないって分かっているんだろう
You know there's no going back
cast a blessing on my cursed role
and feed this bleeding egotistical soul
before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
遠き日の夢を見るたび 生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
Every time I dream of days gone by, I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい 青い 日々 だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
I'll have to be a little stronger first
身分不相応の嫉妬に塗れた
Dripping in jealousy that's a bit too daring
ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
An ecstasy that's just a little bit lacking
誤解も解けないまま私 人を傷つけて
I hurt somebody without ever opening my eyes
一粒の才すらないわ
But there's no talent here, it's clear to see
転がり落ちたジゴロ サイ
The rigged dice falls and rolls
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I ever notice your love and affection
cast a blessing on my cursed heart
why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか神様 教えてくれますか
Pray tell me, God
Pray, tell me, God,
言葉少なに貴方に捧ぐ
I give to you silently,
今に消えてしまいそうなこの命を
my life that's about to burn out.
呼呼 愛しいセピア色した
Ah, and these sepia-toned sights,
何より大事なこの景色を
they're the most precious of all.
もう少し見いていたいよな
I wish I could see them a bit more...
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
If I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The devils on my shoulder never let me be
Obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
Somebody save me, my world is caving in 'cause I thought I deserved it all for free
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by,
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be.
呼呼 美しい蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days,
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind.
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first.
はるはりれ 今踊れ踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance,
恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手歌え
play in the longing of love, sing with cherry blossoms.
離れ紛れ 今を取り戻せ
Lost among flowers, reclaim the present,
水鏡に遊べ さあここで踊れ
play in the water mirror, dance here.
ひゅるりらっぱぱ
Hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa,
一二三四五 あっと言うま時は過ぎてく
One, two, three, four, five, in no time, time passes,
よりどりみどり さまつりばやし
a colorful choice of festival music.
あれもこれも籠り込み 欲に塗れ生きていたい
Throwing everything in, I want to live covered in desire.
人生より道回り道 生きたいように生き耐えよう
Life, detours, roundabout ways—let me live as I wish.
はるはりれ 今踊れ踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance,
恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手歌え
play in the longing of love, sing with cherry blossoms.
離れ紛れ 今を取り戻せ
Lost among flowers, reclaim the present,
水鏡に遊べ さあここで踊れ
play in the water mirror, dance here.
ひゅるりらら ひゅるりらっぱぱ
Hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa...
一二三四五 あっと言うま時は過ぎてく
One, two, three, four, five, in no time, time passes,
酸いも甘いも まつりばやし
tasting the sour and sweet of festival music.
味わいつくしてしまいましょ さあ何から平らげよう
Let's savor it all—what shall we devour first?
人生気付けば矢のごとし 命の花を打ち上げましょう
Life passes like an arrow; let's launch the flower of life.
はるはりれ 今踊れ踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance,
恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手歌え
play in the longing of love, sing with cherry blossoms.
離れ紛れ 今を取り戻せ
Lost among flowers, reclaim the present,
水鏡に遊べ さあここで踊れ
play in the water mirror, dance here.
ひゅるりらら ひゅるりらっぱぱ
Hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa...
花よ花よ 誇りなさい 惑うことなく君のまま
Oh flower, oh flower, be proud—unmistakably remain as you are.
上を向いて御覧なさい 最後の日まで花であれ
Look up and see, be a flower until the very last day.
Turn your face upward and behold—remain a flower until the end.
はるはりれ 今踊れ踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance,
恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手歌え
play in the longing of love, sing with cherry blossoms.
離れ紛れ 今を取り戻せ
Lost among flowers, reclaim the present,
水鏡に遊べ さあここで踊れ
play in the water mirror, dance here.
はるはりれ 今踊れ踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance,
誰彼も遊べ 桜手歌え
everyone play now, sing with cherry blossoms.
離れ離れ でも花火上げて
Separated, separated, but let fireworks rise.
水鏡に遊べ さあここで踊れ
play in the water mirror, dance here.
ひゅるりらら ひゅるりらっぱぱ
Hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa...
あああ
Ah...
ああ したい？ こうしたい？ どうしたい？
Wanna do this? Wanna do that? What you wanna do?
まるで死んでるみたい 石の上にも残念！
It's like I'm dead, what a shame!
でもそんなんじゃAIサーキュレーション
But that's not how it goes. A.I. Circulation.
ようやく始まるストーリー
Today is the day that the story finally begins.
生まれたての卵のような、イン・モーション
Like a newly hatched egg, in motion,
殻から飛び出し いい気味なんて、君は決め顔で せーのっ！
Ready to jump out of its shell, ready, go!
永遠を願った夢に 終わりを告げる朝がきて
The morning comes, signaling the end of my dream of eternity.
お砂糖できたその涙
I stare at those tears made of sugar,
見つめ 見つめ 見つけた心
and find my heart.
甘くほろ苦い キャラメルのように
The ribbons that tangle like bittersweet caramel
絡まるリボンは 呪いの鎧だけど
are like a cursed armor,
この気持ちはそう この気持ちにしか きっとわからないから
but these feelings can only be understood this way.
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you,
一つ一つ、叶えてゆこう
let's make each promise come true, one by one.
僕らの物語は今日に続く、約束
Our story continues to this day, a promise.
色とりどりに真っ黒な歴史 愛おしい私の歴史
A colorful and pitch-black history, my beloved history.
誰もしらない真っ白なページ
A blank page that no one knows about,
更新してゆく
I'll update it.
話したくない澱みは 話したくない喜びで
The frayed edges I don't want to talk about
つぎはぎだらけのこの心 紡ぎ紡いだ空の色
are joys I don't want to let go of.
憧れ恋焦れ待ち焦れ ぜんぶぜんぶぜんぶぜんぶぜんぶぜんぶ
Yearning, yearning with love, yearning and waiting, all of it.
プリンみたいにひっくり返して キャラメル キャラメル my own フレーヴァー
Flip it over like a caramel pudding, my own flavor!
ここが遺したい ここに遺したい 切り離したままじゃ僕はパズルピース＝平和
It hurts here, I want to stay here.
でもそんなんじゃやだ！ もうそんなんじゃだめ！ 僕らキメ顔で.. say no！
But I hate being like that! With a determined look, we say no!
次のカードは自分で選ぶの 運命の赤いリボンを手繰り寄せて
The next card is something I'll choose myself.
この気持ちはそう この気持ちにしか きっとわからないから
These feelings, yes, only these feelings can be understood.
君と手と手繋いで 一つ一つ、叶えてゆこう 僕らの物語は今日に続く、約束
Holding hands with you, let's make each promise come true.
話したくない澱みは 話したくない喜びで
The frayed edges I don't want to talk about...
つぎはぎだらけのこの心 紡ぎ紡いだ空の色
This heart full of patches and stitches...
憧れ恋焦れ待ち焦れ ぜんぶぜんぶぜんぶぜんぶぜんぶぜんぶ
Yearning, yearning with love, yearning and waiting...
プリンみたいにひっくり返して キャラメル キャラメル my own フレーヴァー
Flip it over like a caramel pudding, my own flavor!
ここが遺したい ここに遺したい 切り離したままじゃ僕はパズルピース＝平和
It hurts here, I want to stay here.
でもそんなんじゃやだ！ もうそんなんじゃだめ！ 僕らキメ顔で.. say no！
But I hate being like that! With a determined look, we say no!
次のカードは自分で選ぶの 運命の赤いリボンを手繰り寄せて
The next card is something I'll choose myself.
この気持ちはそう この気持ちにしか きっとわからないから
These feelings, yes, only these feelings can be understood.
君と手と手繋いで 一つ一つ、叶えてゆこう 僕らの物語は今日に続く、約束
Holding hands with you, let's make each promise come true.
色とりどりに真っ黒な歴史 愛おしい私たちの歴史
A colorful and pitch-black history, our beloved history.
残さず食べて全部糧にして 進行していく
Eat it all up, turn it all into nourishment, and march onward.
君と手と手繋いで 一つ一つ、叶えてゆこう
Holding hands with you, let's make each promise come true.
僕らの物語は今日に続く、約束
Our story continues to this day, a promise.
色とりどりに真っ黒な歴史 愛おしい私たちの歴史
A colorful and pitch-black history, our beloved history.
残さず食べて全部糧にして 進行していく
Eat it all up, turn it all into nourishment, and march onward.
君と手と手繋いで 一つ一つ、叶えてゆこう
Holding hands with you, let's make each promise come true.
僕らの物語は今日に続く、約束
Our story continues to this day, a promise.
色とりどりに真っ黒な歴史 愛おしい私たちの歴史
A colorful and pitch-black history, our beloved history.
残さず食べて全部糧にして 進行していく
Eat it all up, turn it all into nourishment, and march onward.
君と手と手繋いで 一つ一つ、叶えてゆこう
Holding hands with you, let's make each promise come true.
僕らの物語は今日に続く、約束
Our story continues to this day, a promise.
残さず食べて全部糧にして 進行していく
Eat it all up, turn it all into nourishment, and march onward.
What are we doing? Welcome back, Calli!
Oh, hi!
You guys look a little tired.
I thought you were posing for the Myth album cover!
It's a misunderstanding!
Yeah, someday, someday.
Did you guys enjoy the song so far?
It's really fun, with a really cute one, Ina!
Caramel ribbon cursetard!
You guys' voices fit really, really well with that song.
You guys' voices fit really well with that song.
Oh, thank you! It's a really cute song.
Me and Ina were like, "What song should we do together?"
And I was like, "Monogatari, please!" And she's like, "Yes!"
Because you're talking to Ninomae Ina'nis, you know, of course I got to say yes.
Because you're talking to Ninomae Ina'nis, of course I got to say yes.
Well, we all like Monogatari, right?
So Kiara could have done it too, huh?
We could have had her doing the...
Now you want to see that. I could do it now.
I should have done it as three people!
It could have been even cuter.
Better do solos, though.
We don't know yet at all.
You guys know I could rap that fast, right?
And it was also a surprise. Impressive!
I did my best. It was like enough to say, "Oh, you know, she did it."
I did my best. It was enough to say, "Yeah, she did it."
Plus the dancing was pretty cool, so.
Oh yeah! Ganbatta! Good job!
Ina too, very impressive.
I did a really challenging rap myself.
The dancing has leveled up so much.
Cute, beautiful, demure.
Oh...
That was a lot of fighting, it was difficult.
Of course, my heart rate shot through the roof, but we did it!
We did it!
We did it! Yeah.
And then, and then, me and Ina did some air guitar.
Oh yeah, bringing...
My original song, Sephiya, close...
Very close song to my heart.
Yeah, I played the guitar that away.
Yeah, yeah, I love the purple guitar. Yeah, felt cute.
Well, what's still missing now?
Oh, there are a couple of songs missing, aren't there?
Like, wow, was so... mine? So... animations.
A lot of, a lot of, you know, and mine and Calli's combination.
Ooh, a song there, boy! What you guys going to see?
I wonder, I wonder, I wonder.
I will just say that the song
for me and Calli was also chosen kind of by, like, suggested by me. Thank you, Calli!
Thank you for being okay with it! It's a nice song, I guess. Yeah, I don't want to spoil anything, but it's pretty good.
Yes.
And my solo will be, uh...
(Epic and hype) So, you guys...
Epic and hype.
So, why didn't you choose it? Can you give a hint? Can you give a hint?
I know it's about to happen pretty soon here, but...
No, hey, no, dammit! No! All right, all right.
Why? I'm a toddler, why? Yes!
We still have a lot of our show left over.
So, don't do not, there's lots more. Stay with us! Stay right here!
Don't look away, and continue to watch until the end!
And you'll have the hashtag, don't forget that.
Okay, hashtag.
Are you ready to move on?
Move on? Okay.
What should we do? Should we, should we play with the camera?
What do you want to do? What do you want to do the most?
I know what to do. Ho!
What are you going to do?
Number seven, oh no. That's something violent, right?
Not something violent... I didn't She's going to do something violent.
She's going to do something violent! Hey! Yeah!
Hey!
Dear God, I've come to repent my sins
Let your blood wash me clean for I'm, I'm, I'm...
A rotten girl
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
The temptation flowing through my veins
I'm bounded by these shackles of shame
I promised I'd indulge no more
But my heart I can't ignore
In my dreams they're turning up the heat
I'm a dirty, rotten girl
On lock, underneath the bleachers
Just watch, look beyond the smoke and mirrors
Heart struck? Shun the nun believer
Our operation would never be complete
Red hot, tension with each whisper
Snapshot, quiet moans and muffled whimpers
Come on, can't you feel the fever rising up to the sky?
As testaments echo, fear ignites beneath my skin
The lord sayeth, "Halt thy child, don't give into sin"
It's driving me crazy
The urge to forsake thee
Yet, something shifts within this wicked bliss
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
Student council breathing down my neck
I wonder if they're hiding from me
Forbidden fruits before my eyes
And a taste that's so divine
My regrets rewriting history
I'm a sad, pathetic girl
Someone please tell me what to do because honestly, I just can't stop
I've been trying so hard and I can't stop what would god think?
And, I- I know I'm supposed to be a good girl, but somehow, I just can't control myself
Every time I see them
Touching skin to skin
My mind goes
Ah
Could Eve be our idol? Could she lead us through the light?
With all redeemed disciples of her lemon driven bite
Can somebody save me?
The urge to forsake thee
Still, something shifts within this wicked bliss
The power resting in my hands
For my god has other plans
In salvation I can live my life as an ordinary girl
I can't resist it anymore
'Cause I smell slow burn galore
All the trauma from a cobblestone could never be the devil in me
An honest sinner till I die
What's the harm if I don't mind?
With the paddle that empowers me
I can live a sinful life
チェックワンツー！
Check one, two!
チェックワンツー！Yeah!
Check one, two! Yeah!
あーあ もう無理! 文化祭
Ah... I can't do this anymore! School festival
言葉に ダンスに… キャパオーバーです
With words, with dance... I'm at full capacity!
心配無用のおまじない
A spell that you needn't worry about
きっと報われる その努力
Surely that effort will be rewarded
笑顔になれ! ドキドキしてる
Put on a smile! My heart is pounding
ありえないくらい本気だし
I'm dead serious, more than you'd believe
魔法がかかる 今日限り ヒーロータイム
Magic takes hold, hero time for today only
何とぞね Let's go!
Please and thank you, let's go!
baby kiss♡ 隠さずに 気持ち伝えてよ!
baby kiss, don't hide it, convey your feelings!
好き? 好き! 相思相愛好き!
Love? Love! Mutual love, love!
メイク崩れても 髪が乱れても
Even if my makeup runs, even if my hair gets messy
好き! 好き! 絶対忘れない青春の1ページ Hi!
Love! Love! The unforgettable page of youth, Hi!
あーあ 超気持ちいい 文化祭
Ah... This feels so good, school festival
隣で笑ってる 君のおかげだ
Thanks to you smiling right beside me
弱気な私 変えてくれた
You changed my timid self
絶対最強のパートナー まじでありがとう
Truly my strongest partner, thank you so much
カクセイしてる ファンの火力マシマシで
Awakening, with fans' firepower turned all the way up
魔法かかりまくる 終わりかけ ヒーロータイム
Magic in full effect, ending-soon hero time
延長、ね? Let's go!
Extension, okay? Let's go!
baby kiss♡ 隠さずに 気持ち伝えてよ!
baby kiss, don't hide it, convey your feelings!
好き? 好き! 相思相愛好き!
Love? Love! Mutual love, love!
おやつ食べたいし 帰宅していいですか?
I want a snack, can I go home now?
ダメ! ダメ! ごめんうそうそ
No! No! Just kidding, just kidding
こちらこそ帰さない! Hi!
I won't let you go either! Hi!
TakaMori for five years! Can you guys keep it going?! いくよー!
TakaMori for five years! Can you guys keep it going?! Here we go!
かりちゃんは超かわいい?
Is Calli-chan super cute?
きあらちゃんは超かわいい?
Is Kiara-chan super cute?
Big Ups! Everybody! Danke schön! Are you ready? 3, 2, 1, Go!
魔法解けちゃうね… 最後に聞かせてよ
The magic is wearing off... Let me hear it one last time
好き? 好き! 好き!
Love? Love! Love!
大きな声で 好き!
With a loud voice, love!
メイク崩れても 髪が乱れても
Even if my makeup runs, even if my hair gets messy
好き! 好き! 絶対忘れない青春の1ページ Hi!
Love! Love! The unforgettable page of youth, Hi!
ななななななな Yeah!
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na Yeah!
ダンダダン ダンダダン ダンダダン
Dandadan, dandadan, dandadan
恥ずがめ悪い奴ら あんたじゃ務まんねえとも可能かもう
Shameless bad guys, even you couldn't handle this alone
クワブラクワブラクワブラ 目にも止まらぬ早さ
Kuwabara, kuwabara, kuwabara, moving faster than lightning
下等化てだいじゃあまた 俺はもう一人のあなた さあどちゃん かやちゃん
Lowering form, see you again, I am the other you, Sada-chan, Kaya-chan
諦めの悪い野暮な奴等
These are stubborn, unyielding folks,
あんたなんかじゃ束になってもかなわん
you could band together and still not stand a chance.
クワバラ、クワバラ、クワバラ
Kuwabara, kuwabara, kuwabara,
目にも留まらん速さ（Hey）
moving faster than lightning struck (Hey)!
欲を剥がしたんなら文字通りお疲れ様やん
If you've stripped your greed, literally, good work to you.
入れた、入れた、入れた、入れた、入れた
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in!
して、入れた先で霧は晴れた
Beyond where I entered, the fog cleared up.
盾と矛が上手く噛み合ったら 瞳が重なったら
When shield and spear mesh, when our gazes meet,
心、体、頭、みなぎっていくんだが 背中に今羽が生えたならば
heart, body, head overflowing, if wings sprout on our backs,
暗闇からさらば (Ay)
we'll bid farewell to the darkness (Ay)!
飛び立っていく彼方 (Ay)
Flying off to the horizon (Ay)...
心、体、頭、懐かしい温かさ 足元に今花が咲いたならば
Heart, body, head, nostalgic warmth, if flowers bloom at our feet,
暗闇からさらば (Ay)
we'll bid farewell to the darkness (Ay)!
飛び立っていく彼方 (Woah!) 飛び立っていく彼方
Flying off to the horizon (Woah!)...
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
Living over and over, inside you and me,
まぶたの裏や耳の中 胸の奥に息づいてるメロディ リズムに (Yeah)
behind our eyelids and inside our ears, the melody breathing deep within, to the rhythm (Yeah)!
今日も三途の川のど真ん中 積み上げてく Top of Top
Today too, right in the middle of the Sanzu River, piling to the top!
鬼とチャンバラ The lyrical chainsaw massacre
Sword-fighting with demons, the lyrical chainsaw massacre.
渡る大海原 花うた Singin' "Sha-la-la"
Crossing the open ocean, singing a flower song 'Sha-la-la'...
払いたいのであらば末代までの札束
If you want to pay it off, bundles of cash till the end of time.
誰が開けたかパンドラ あとは何がっても知らんがな
Who opened Pandora's box? Whatever comes next, I don't care!
何百年待たが超久しぶりのシャバだ
Having waited centuries, it's been ages since we hit the real world.
ガキや若葉まどっちきちいんじゃねえよバカが 今確実に目が合ったな
Kids and fledglings, don't get ahead of yourselves, idiots! Our eyes just met.
入れた、入れた、入れた、入れた、入れた
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in!
眠りあきた先で君が待っていた
Beyond endless slumber, you were waiting there.
盾と矛が肩を抱き合ったら 怒りが消え合ったら
When shield and spear embrace, when anger fades away,
心、体、頭、みなぎっていくんだが 背中に今羽が生えたならば
heart, body, head overflowing, if wings sprout on our backs,
暗闇からさらば 飛び立っていく彼方
we'll bid farewell to the darkness, flying off to the horizon.
心、体、頭、懐かしい温かさ 足元に今花が咲いたならば
Heart, body, head, nostalgic warmth, if flowers bloom at our feet,
暗闇からさらば 飛び立っていく彼方
we'll bid farewell to the darkness, flying off to the horizon.
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
Living over and over, inside you and me,
まぶたの裏や耳の中 胸の奥に息づいてるメロディ リズムに
behind our eyelids and inside our ears, the melody breathing deep, to the rhythm.
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the Muses whisper "Truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war, but no one 's keeping score
The hands of fate play tug-of-war, but no one's keeping score.
stay the course and be tenacious
'cause the future is a game of chance .
Stay the course and be tenacious, 'cause the future is a game of chance.
the chips are down , but i 'm all in
i play until i win ！
The chips are down, but I'm all in, I play until I win!
i 'm not gonna give up now ,
the wheels of fortune circle back around .
I'm not gonna give up now, the wheels of fortune circle back around.
a new turn in the betting ring ;
a maze of outcomes drawn in golden string .
A new turn in the betting ring, a maze of outcomes drawn in golden string.
and through this tangled thread , i see what 's up ahead :
a wild chase , a frantic pace ,
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead: a wild chase, a frantic pace,
i got to try my luck , i 'm spinning fate
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate.
( ah … la da da da da da da
i 'm always spinning fate
Ah... la da da da da da da, I'm always spinning fate,
whoah yeah )
Whoah yeah!
spin the roulette , see where it falls
testing the limits and betting it all—
Spin the roulette, see where it falls, testing the limits and betting it all—
round and around , jumping into the circle
over and over , a test of will
Round and around, jumping into the circle, over and over, a test of will.
oh , the game is never easy
and the outcome is a mystery .
Oh, the game is never easy and the outcome is a mystery.
but these are fates worth betting on ,
their threads unbroken .
But these are fates worth betting on, their threads unbroken.
called to life by flaxen string ,
casting lots together at the start of everything .
Called to life by flaxen string, casting lots together at the start of everything.
i 'm not gonna give up yet ,
i spin back ' round with every chance i get ,
I'm not gonna give up yet, I spin back 'round with every chance I get,
the wheel turns and the die is cast ,
the time has come for fate to change at last .
The wheel turns and the die is cast, the time has come for fate to change at last.
and if it 's black or red , i 'm moving up ahead !
a perfect chance , a daring dance
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead! A perfect chance, a daring dance,
i 'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
( ooh la la la
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands. (Ooh la la la...)
i 'm taking fate into my hands
whoah , yeah
I'm taking fate into my hands, whoah, yeah!
and through this tangled thread , i see what 's up ahead
and through this tangled thread , i see what 's up ahead )
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead!
Oh, now that I'm thinking about it,
Yeah, it's only like two minutes.
That was like a workout.
I guess it's because all the zoomers say like it's shorts nowadays, huh?
I guess it's because all the zoomers like shorts nowadays, huh?
That's what everybody says.
Not you.
Certainly not.
Well yeah, unfortunately, this was also the last song for this live.
Yay!
But the music video for our 5th anniversary song, 'Fortune Spinner', will premiere on the Hololive English Official YouTube channel right after this concert,
But the music video for our 5th anniversary song, 'Fortune Spinner',
will premiere on the Hololive English Official YouTube channel right after this concert,
so make sure you stick around, okay? Don't miss it.
Make sure you watch it a lot, and stream it a lot.
そうですね。そうですね。
That's right. That's right.
We still have some celebrating to do, right?
That's right. I think it's time, because it's the end, that we kind of celebrate ourselves here. Five years! Are we ready for that?
That's right. I think it's time, because it's the end,
to celebrate ourselves here. Five years! Are we ready for that?
Yes.
Yes, we are ready, okay? Let's do it! Let's do it!
Yes, we're ready! Okay, let's do it! Let's do it!
What is that cake over there that is not mine?
Baby, baby, can we have it? Come on, come on!
Can we? Can we? Look how delicious it looks!
Can we? Look how delicious it looks!
No, no, I can't see it. Oh, never mind, I can't see it.
It's almost bigger than Ina. Oh yeah. Hey, stop, stop, stop, not now, not now!
It's almost bigger than Ina. Oh yeah.
Hey, stop, stop, stop! Not now, not now!
Hey, don't pick off the strawberry! Hold your horses!
Hey, don't pick off the strawberries! Hold your horses!
Let's eat it later and celebrate. Eat it later.
And look at the trophies! Yeah, I know. We can do an award show, right?
Did they actually get our trophies? Yeah, they were listening. Thank you.
They followed our shopping list accordingly.
Five years deserve an award. Yeah, we have so many meaningful accomplishments, so let's see what they all are, okay?
Five years deserve an award. Yeah, we have so many meaningful accomplishments,
so let's see what they all are, okay?
Okay! What's going to be?
Okay! What's it gonna be?
Yeah. Should I start? I'll take mine.
Oh, God bless you. God bless you.
Cha, cha, cha, cha. Oh, let's go.
Sorry, not trying to disrupt your award. What did you get? What did you get?
Sorry, not trying to disrupt your award.
What did you get? What did you get?
My award is, uh, let's see, uh...
Most Meals Cooked Award ~ Takanashi Kiara ~
[Award: Most Meals Cooked Award ~ Takanashi Kiara ~]
I think it says Most Meals Cooked. Cooked the most!
She's cooking in HoloEN!
Let her cook! Let her cook, let her keep doing it! She has been cooking a lot. She has a lot of meals.
Let her cook! Let her keep doing it!
She has been cooking a lot. She has a lot of meals.
Yeah. Cooked a lot of meals. A lot.
Yes, thank you. I think that's what that's about. Mostly it's about, uh, you know, me living a healthy lifestyle and then cooking many meals at home.
Yes, thank you. I think that's what that's about.
Mostly it's about, uh, you know, me living a healthy lifestyle and cooking many meals at home.
I wish I could cook for you girls someday.
I hope you guys enjoyed my performances today. I am so proud to stand here with my gen-mates, even on this day, after so many years.
I hope you guys enjoyed my performances today.
I am so proud to stand here with my gen-mates, even on this day, after so many years.
I will continue to work hard, of course, and so that I can maybe get even more awards.
I will continue to work hard, of course,
so that I can maybe get even more awards.
I will put this on my shelf at home where my cats will also probably put a lot of fur on it, or knock it down.
I will put this on my shelf at home where my cats
will probably put a lot of fur on it, or knock it down.
Now, is it out of real glass? I got to be a little bit careful. Careful. Yeah.
Now, is it out of real glass? I gotta be a little bit careful. Careful. Yeah.
Thank you guys so much. I love you, Kiara. It's been an honor so far, so let's do our best together.
Thank you guys so much. I love you, Kiara.
It's been an honor so far, so let's do our best together.
Okay, what is this award?
Who's next? Who's next? Is it Ninomainis?
Me? Oh, could my award be, let's see...
Most violent? Yikes! What's violent? You do it to yourself? No, no, highway.
My award is... yeah. Oh, yes. Oh, yes. I already got it.
Most Time Spent on the Floor Award ~ Ninomae Ina'nis ~
[Award: Most Time Spent on the Floor Award ~ Ninomae Ina'nis ~]
Oh, that I believe. Yes!
Thank you, thank you. I know you guys probably think I would never get this award, but you know, I worked so hard to seriously fail the floor.
Thank you, thank you. I know you guys probably think I would never get this award,
but you know, I worked so hard to seriously fail the floor.
And yeah, not only did I stand on the floor, I, you know, really did my best to, you know, practice dancing and singing this year
And yeah, not only did I stand on the floor, I, you know,
really did my best to, you know, practice dancing and singing this year
to perform well with you guys, and I hope that you guys see that as well. Thank you so much for all your support.
to perform well with you guys, and I hope that you guys see that as well.
Thank you so much for all your support.
I'll continue to do my best with these girls. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's keep doing it, thank you, and not least.
I'll continue to do my best with these girls. Yeah, let's keep doing it. Thank you. And last but not least,
Oh, what could it be? What could it be? What could it be? A little sneezer?
Oh, what could it be? What could it be? A little sneezer?
The most sneezes in the Myth 5th Anniversary showcase. Most blessed.
Okay. Well, actually, my trophy is for...
Best Worst Luck Award ~ Mori Calliope ~
[Award: Best Worst Luck Award ~ Mori Calliope ~]
Best worst luck, especially in games where there are microtransactions.
That's not so possible. Yeah, I mean, I've seen it happen in real life.
Every time with the dedication, the determination to pull a signed card or not, I'm not going to give up yet.
Every time with the dedication, the determination to pull a signed card or not,
I'm not going to give up yet.
We're going to be very sappy. Okay, go ahead.
I really like that line. I'm not going to...
not give up yet because, because
I'd like to think that
we're not gonna give up yet,
because there's still so much that I want to do,
uh the three of us together, together,
you know,
um and I didn't think that I would be here five years from the start with you guys.
Same.
Yeah, I really thought I'd be out of here. But now
I can't I can't see a future where I'm not here with you guys. So for now,
I can't— I can't see a future where I'm not here with you guys. So for now,
That's her song!
Okay, okay, okay, she's she's she's shh. Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, she's... shh. Okay.
So because of that, I'm not gonna give up yet.
I don't want to give up yet. So let's do our best.
Oh, are they playing?
Oh, yeah, the wrapping music is playing.
I was just gonna start talking about nothing
because that annoys me when they play the jingle to talk to you guys.
This morning I ate a bagel and it had
guchis on it. It was delicious, but it went over my budget.
It didn't make trouble with my trainer. Okay.
Anyway, anniversary 5,
Yeah, you can't get rid of me.
Out here.
You can't get rid of any of us. Any of us.
Fair buddy. All good things come to an end, unfortunately, but
thank you so much to the hololive EN community for supporting us continuously for 5 years.
Thank you to the gurlies today and all the staff and sound that supported us also,
for the celebration, who gave us the trophies. Yeah. Once again,
congratulations to us. To us! Yeah!
Yay!
Happy 5 years! Yay! Yay!
Thank you!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Peace! Yeah, thanks guys.
Did you guys forget the merch?
Oh, merch! Merch, please! The merchandise!
Next is the merchandise announcement.
We have Hololive English Myth 5th Anniversary Celebration merch being released.
Let's look at the details. Check it out.
First up, we've got the Mirror Acrylic Panel.
It's designed so that the surroundings and background of the illustration have a metallic mirrored vibe.
Oh, so cool! I absolutely love this illustration. Hope you guys do too.
Next up, we have
the Collection Cards.
These cards feature a shiny metallic finish,
and you can choose from three different designs.
Also, the backside is matching for us all.
Make sure to get the one from your oshi for sure!
Next up, we have the Coin Medals.
Our shiny 5th anniversary commemorative coin medals, there's one design for each member.
And the backside also have a common design.
They come in an antique gold-plated finish inside the original packaging. Ooh, so shiny!
Oh man, everything looks so good, but I'm especially interested in what we have to show you guys next.
Next up, we have the Anniversary Hat - Mori Calliope!
This one uses a soft, fluffy fabric.
The Death Sensei part is removable so you can also rock it without him.
Make sure that you check it out. It's super stylish! I love the shape so much. And all of my Member Deadbeats voted on it together, so hope that you guys will enjoy.
Next up, we have mine, the Anniversary Hat from Takanashi Kiara.
Looks like this! Decorative parts are removable. It can be worn reversibly,
inside out, so you'll have a different color then. And it's a bucket hat style design, which we didn't have before for me, very fashionable, I must say.
Last but not least, we have my hat, the Anniversary Hat, Ninomae Ina'nis.
The ribbon part is removable and the patches are super cute too!
You can wear it to become Takodachi. Yes!
And yeah, you can mix and match with or without the ribbon for different looks.
So everybody, be sure to check our merch out! And that concludes our fifth-year anniversary stream! Ultimate Myth!
there's an answer out there somewhere
when the muses whisper "truth or dare?"
the hands of fate play tug-of-war
but no one's keeping score
stay the course and be tenacious
'cause the future is a game of chance.
the chips are down, but i'm all in
i play until i win!
i'm not gonna give up now,
the wheels of fortune circle back around.